http://www.windells.com/privacy-policy

Register NowParentsAcademyCamp StoreNEWS
Windells ONLINE PRIVACY POLICYWe would like to thank you for your support and want you to know that your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy is provided to explain how information is collected on our website and how that information is handled once it has been collected.Please note that this privacy policy may change at any time. While using the highcascade.com website you accept the terms and conditions described in this privacy policy. For the latest changes to our privacy policy click the privacy link on our website at any time.Windells RegistrationPersonal information is gathered by Windells during camp and contest registrations processes, brochure requests, contest submissions, and e-newsletter subscriptions. During these processes, your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services may be collected. Your account user name and password are collected at this time as for processes requiring a myHCSC account creation.Please note that for processes requiring a myWindells account creation, your user name is your email address and you may create your own unique password. If you forget your password you can request to have your password emailed to your email address.For security reasons, Windells does not store sensitive credit card information on our servers. To view your account history in your myWindells account click here at any time to view your Windells camp session and/or contest registration history as well your personal contact information.Remember your user name is your email address.Personal information is also gathered by Windells when you request a brochure or subscribe to the What's up Windells™ email newsletter. When requesting to subscribe to What's up Windells™ or a brochure we may gather your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. If at any time you would like to be removed from our email list please send an email to office@wearecamp.com and type Remove in the subject line. if you receive our monthly e-newsletter or our What's up Windells™ e-newsletter, you may opt out clicking on the embedded unsubscribe link.Updating Personal InformationIf you have created a myWindells account, log into your myWindells account to update your personal information online. You can also call 503.206.8520 or email office@wearecamp.com and we can change your information for you. For security purposes you will be asked to disclose account information in order to change your username and/or password.Information UsageThe information collected during registration is used to primarily to process your camp registration, send you registration related materials and emails , and/or send brochure. Your account information is maintained privately on our secure web servers. Occasionally, unless otherwise requested during the check out process, Windells may share information about our customer’s with affiliated companies and other reputable third party vendors in order to enhance the service we provide. Windells requires this information be handled securely and responsibly. Windells does not sell, share, or rent email addresses and does not condone unsolicited email.Windells will disclose any information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request. Remember, Windells will not use or transfer the personal information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.CookiesSmall text files stored on your computer’s hard drive, cookies are used by Windells to enhance your shopping experience. Cookies are also used to speed up the browsing experience and web site performance while using the Windells web site. They are used to personalize your experience while using our web site. Finally, we also use cookies to remember your information when you come back to our site.This functionality is activated when cookies in your browser are enabled. To turn off this functionality simply disable cookies in your browser.Privacy of YouthWindells does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should have their parents fill out required registration or catalog information.SecurityThe security of the information regarding your registration is very important to us. We use a third party vendor to process all camp registration which has established and maintains reasonable security procedures to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We use a variety of industry-standard security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. For example, credit card numbers are encrypted in a secure database which is located behind a firewall. Personal information and such encrypted credit card numbers collected are stored in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public. All credit card and registration information supplied by users is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. “Perfect security,” however, does not exist on the Internet. Although your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we will disclose personal information about an individual user if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with an applicable law or valid legal process.Questions and ConcernsIf you have any question or concerns in regard to our privacy policy, please contact Windells at:WindellsCamp5955 E Hwy. 26Sandy, OR 97055503.206.8520office@wearecamp.com
Register Now
